原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     VioletCheng  五天  克里斯托啊托
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     Caroline
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
扮巴仔超人
我们最爱的辛普森一家
第三十一季  第六集
怎么  太早了
What, too soon?
停下
Avast there.
现在变道太晚了  亲们
It be too late to alter course, matey.
每个小海湾里都有海盗等着
And there be pirates lurking in every cove.
快点开吧
Get to the ride.
他们拍照了吗
Did they get a picture?
欢迎来到我们首届由学生创作的
Welcome to our first-ever night of dramatic scenes
戏剧之夜
written by our students.
我们应该把手机和呼机静音吗
Should we silence our cell phones and pagers?
不不不  拜托就开着吧
No, no, no, please, I beg you, leave them on.
这里有些可以吃的糖果
An-And here-here's some candy to unwrap.
现在有请他们表演CW台《河谷镇》新剧情
And now, an new scene from the CW's Riverdale.
猪头  老爹快餐店有一起谋杀案
Jughead, there's been a murder at Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe
只有小孩才能解决
and it's up to us kids to solve it.
我现在没法管这件事
I can't deal with that right now.
我老爸在监狱里  唯一能把他弄出来的办法
My dad's in jail and the only way to get him out
就是下药
is to try drugs.
我们都有了穆斯的宝宝
We're both pregnant with Big Moose's babies.
春田小学
慢着  所以这出戏是基于
Wait. So this is a play based on a YouTube
一个小孩打电子游戏的油管视频
of kids playing a video game?
-没错  -终于
- That's right. - It's about time.
想拿到他们的能量饮料[堡垒之夜道具]
Okay, to get their chug jugs,
我可以把他们一个个狙击掉
I could snipe these guys out one by one,
但更聪明的做法
but the smarter move is to plant a charge
是在他们攻击平台的底部放一个炸药
at the base of their attack platform
等他们一着陆就炸上天
and skull-splat 'em when they land.
朋友们  如果你们了解更多游戏技巧
Hey, guys, if you want more game hacks like this,
请给我们点赞并订阅我们的频道
be sure to smash our like button and subscribe to our channel.
订阅
接下来  夜晚模式的失败集锦
Up next, night vision fails.
这怎么能算一部戏
How is this a play?
先生  电子游戏通关直播
Well, sir, video game walk-throughs
是这些孩子能接触的最有叙事性的东西
are the only narrative most of these kids have been exposed to.
-这是他们的贝克特[大主教]  -谁
- This is their Becket. - Who?
蒙面歌王
你是特里·布莱德肖吗
Are you Terry Bradshaw?
不  是唐尼·奥斯蒙
No. It's, uh, Donny Osmond.
伯纳  《成长的烦恼》里的伯纳
Boner. Boner from Growing Pains.
你们都错了  我真正的身份是
You're all wrong. My real identity is...
弗拉沃尔·弗拉维
Flavor Flav!
弗拉沃尔·弗拉维  我听说过你
Flavor Flav? I've heard of you.
我经常听说你
I've heard of you so much.
我超爱你的电影  书  或是音乐
I am such a huge fan of your movies, books, or music.
我也能装的很吃惊
I can also pretend to be impressed.
剧终
The end.
醒醒  下一个就是丽莎
Wake up. Lisa's next.
别啊  我在做美梦呢
Oh, no, please. I'm having the best dream.
我在自己温暖舒适的坟墓里
I was in my warm, cozy grave.
我要梦到自己在柔软可爱的棺材里
Well, I'm gonna dream about me in a soft, cuddly crypt.
令人惊奇的是  接下来的作品并非基于
Amazingly, this next piece is not based on something
你在手机或加油泵上看到的东西
you watch on your phone or a gas pump,
而是一部实实在在地地道道的戏剧
but is actually an honest-to-goodness play,
由丽莎·感谢上帝你回来了·辛普森带来
by Lisa "Thank God You're a Throwback" Simpson.
请欣赏
And so I give you
《与淡啤酒度过的漫长一天》
Long Day's Journey Into Light Beer.
我的啤酒呢  马娇丽
Where's my beer, Marjorie?
我花了一天时间确保这啤酒是冷的
I spent all day making sure this beer was cold.
我做错了选择
Aah! I make bad choices.
丽莎学希伯特一家不要太像
Lisa's really nailed the Hibberts.
老兄  我的口头禅
Uh, yo, dude, my catchphrases
跟我的弹弓一样过时
are as outdated as my slingshot.
我的天哪
Ay, caramba!
妈妈  做一个不仅有社会道德心
Oh, Mom, it's so hard being a straight-A student
还能写很棒的戏剧的好学生真难
with a social conscience who writes amazing plays.
这个家里唯一可靠的就是你
The only stable thing in this house is you,
你让每天都跟昨天一样
making every day the same as the last.
完全一样
Exactly the same.
就跟咖啡机说的一样
Like the coffee maker says,
振作精神
things will perk up.
我以为是你做的咖啡
I thought you were the coffee maker.
你可以从咖啡渗滤壶身上学到很多
You can learn a lot from percolators.
珍惜每天每分每秒
Make the most of the daily grind.
妈妈这个角色真是令人犯困
The mother character is such a snooze.
拉尔夫根本不能跟她形成冲突
Ralph has nothing to play against.
他们觉得我无聊
They think I'm boring.
这出戏是有关我们家的
This play is about us!
今天我决定做一个赛车手
Today I decided to be a race car driver,
于是我去了  然后我又不去了
so I was, then I quit.
我也有令人激动的消息
I also have exciting news.
我把四块小肥皂屑
I converted four soap slivers
融化成了一块新肥皂
into practically a new bar.
这个世界就是这么看我的吗
Is this how the world sees me-- as a...
现在的孩子怎么说没劲
How do the kids say lame these days?
我们说没劲儿  你真没劲儿
We say lame-o, you lame-o.
吸吸  我感觉像是迷雾里的
Suck, suck. And I felt like the ghost
一个鬼魂
belonging to the fog.
迷雾就是鬼魂的海洋
And the fog was the ghost of the sea.
吸吸
Suck, suck.
你真的觉得我那么无聊吗
You really think I'm that boring?
丽莎  你让别人感到不开心了
Lisa, you made someone feel sad,
这可不是家庭剧该造成的结局
which is not what a drama about a family is supposed to do.
马姬  能合张影吗
Marge, could we get a picture?
好的
Okay.
春田第一教堂
现在有泡过黄瓜的洗礼盆
所以世世代代
So all the generations...
无聊  他们觉得我无聊
Boring. They think I'm boring.
我要让他们看看谁才无聊
I'll show them who's boring.
今早  马姬·辛普森强烈自愿前来
Now, this morning, Marge Simpson has insistently volunteered
读一段
to read a passage.
她说她将融入自己的理解
She says she's gonna bring her own spin to it.
现在来读一段《约翰福音》  18章38节
Now, a reading from John, 18:38,
庞修斯·彼拉多和耶稣之间的对话
between Pontius Pilate and Jesus.
马姬  马姬  马姬
Marge! Marge! Marge!
天呀  耶稣
Hey-a Jesus,
你怎么个回事
what's a matter for you?
你说你是个国王
You saying youse a king?
他是个罗马人  所以我才用这种口音
He was Roman, that's why I'm doing the accent.
总之  耶稣回答  我觉得耶稣应该
Anyhoo, Jesus answered, and I think it might have gone
差不多长这样
something like this.
我不是国王  我是个木匠
I'm not a king, I'm a carpenter.
一个犹太木匠
A Jewish carpenter.
我唯一能搞定的就是美国大学入学考试
The only thing I nail are my SATs.
然后  庞修斯对老者说
So then, Pontius says to the elders,
这个是个耶稣  他看起来是个好人
"This-a Jesus, he-a look like a nice-a guy."
没人像这个样子讲话
Nobody talk-a like-a that.
我能说一句流畅的话
I make a nice-a sentence.
就像妈妈之前教的一样
Just like-a Mama used to construct.
我们能听勒弗乔伊布道吗
Can we just hear Lovejoy's sermon, please?
对  马姬  有点眼力见
Yeah, Marge, read the room.
你比我们更需要这些  女士
You need this more than we do, lady.
无聊  一个全优的女童子军
Boring. That's what this straight-A Girl Scout
变成了这样  无聊
has become-- boring.
你刚刚在鬼门关走了一遭
You just had a near-death experience.
真让人兴奋
That's exciting.
你的人生真是精彩  妈妈
What a rich life you lead, Mom.
我要去睡了
I'm going to bed.
这真的会改变你无聊的名声
That will really turn around your boring reputation.
别担心  侯默  我去砍木头
Don't worry, Homer, I'll chop the wood.
像往常一样
Like always.
什么都要我做
I have to do everything.
树都要我砍
Even chop the trees.
我知道她可以把砍树的功夫用到哪去
I know where she can put that chopping to good use.
侯默的脖子
Homer's neck?
不  他根本没脖子  有更好的用处
No. He doesn't have one. Something better.
把右手放低一点  能更有力
Lower your right hand. Gives you more power.
谢谢
Thanks, um...
保拉  帕蒂的朋友
Paula. Friend of Patty's.
我们在燃烧吧女人认识的
We met at Burning Woman.
树砍得不错
Nice job on that wood.
我也出力了
I helped.
对  你也出力了
Yeah, you helped, all right.
你帮吊床亲吻大地了
You helped that hammock kiss the ground.
马姬  我不知道你是否知道
Marge, I don't know if you know this,
但是我是伐木运动的顶级竞争者
but I'm a top-level contender at Timbersports.
那太有意思了
That's so interesting.
出色是什么感觉
How does it feel to be magnificent?
我来展示给你看
I'll show you.
是个有趣的爱好
That is a fascinating hobby.
伐木运动不止是个爱好
Timbersports is more than a hobby.
是你在业余时间付出的没有回报的激情
It's an unpaid passion that you do in your spare time.
现在  咱们去树林里
Now, we're going to the woods.
-你在干什么  -呼吸
- What are you doing? - Breathing.
这辈子第一次呼吸
Breathing for the first time in my life.
我能做一件事
Can I do one thing
缓解你肩部的紧张吗
for the knots in your shoulders?
当然
Sure.
别太...
Not so...
现在  为了激励你砍木头
Now, to motivate your chopping,
想象那些让你生气的东西
think of things that make you mad.
没什么能真的让我生气
Oh, nothing really makes me mad.
妈妈  丽莎不肯待在自己的想象气泡里
Mom, Lisa won't stay on her side of the thought bubble.
你的小命还剩五秒
You have five seconds to live.
你也是  白痴  我们在同一个气泡里
So do you, idiot. We're in the same bubble.
我的遗言是丽莎是个小辣鸡
My final words are Lisa sucks!
她真有天赋
She's a natural.
*我走进森林里*
*I walked into the forest*
*森林碧绿又美丽*
*So beautiful and green*
*我看见有个女人*
*And there I saw a woman*
*砍倒了一棵树*
*Who was chopping down a tree*
*锯末飞扬*
*The sawdust was flyin'*
*她踩着圆木旋转*
*She was spinnin' on a log*
*她的腰上系着工具带*
*On her waist was strapped a tool belt*
*上面有把百得牌的电锯*
*With a Black & Decker saw*
*呜  呜  拉动绳子*
*Vroom, vroom, pull the cord*
*嗡  嗡  再拉一下*
*Buzz, buzz, just one more*
*吼  吼  多么刺激*
*Roar, roar, what a thrill*
*和伐木工在一起*
*With Lumberjill*
*呜  呜  拉动绳子*
*Vroom, vroom, pull the cord*
*嗡  嗡  再拉一下*
*Buzz, buzz, just one more*
*吼  吼  多么刺激*
*Roar, roar, what a thrill*
*和伐木工在一起*
*With Lumberjill*
春田伐木运动职业业余选手混合赛
原春田森林
我是奇普·班扬
I'm Chip Bunyan, eh,
欢迎来到春田镇伐木运动职业业余选手混合赛
and welcome to the Springfield Timbersports Pro-Am.
我身边是前NBA解说员暴躁·瓦特金
I'm here with former NBA analyst Anger Watkins.
伐木运动  伐木的运动吗
Timbersports. Timber sports?
我就扯了一个助理医师的内衣带子
I snap one P.A.'s bra strap,
结果我就到这儿来了
and this is where I land?
这件事中是谁在背后捅我刀子
Who is the Lebron of this thing?
指勒布朗作为骑士的中心人物  2010年转去了热火
被当时的球迷和队友所不理解  认为是背叛之举
没人告诉我
No one will tell me.
他叫马特·科加
His name is Matt Cogar.
马特·科加  美国顶级伐木运动员
他的绰号是美洲狮吗
Is his nickname The Cougar?
不是  是马特
No, his nickname is Matt.
马特不是绰号
Matt isn't a nickname.
就是个名字
It's a name name.
要不是我太害怕松鼠
I'd storm out of here right now
我早就从这里暴走了
if I weren't so terrified of squirrels.
把我的钱拿去  拿去
Take my money! Take it!
我很高兴妈妈有了热爱的事物
I'm glad Mom's found a passion,
但我希望她不用砍光所有那些树
but I wish she didn't have to kill all those trees.
我读到过  树是全球变暖的罪魁祸首
I read that trees are the cause of global warming.
你在哪读到的
Where'd you read that?
我四年级的新科学书
My new fourth grade science book.
埃克森美孚向你证明科学的虚伪
由米奇·麦康奈尔撰写序言
埃克森美孚  世界最大的非政府石油天然气生产商
他们已经开始了  展示着许多的森林智慧
And they're off, displaying lots of forest gumption, eh?
第一位选手是内尔森·孟茨
First we have Nelson Muntz.
他今年十岁  但是肥肠艰难的十年
He's ten years old, but, man, is it a hard ten.
看  那是我儿子
Hey. That's my boy.
他的爬杆技术是跟他妈妈学的
He gets his pole skills from his mama.
马姬·辛普森领先了
Oh! Marge Simpson takes the lead!
没人预料到  因为没人在看
No one saw this coming, because no one was watching.
她的动力会是什么呢
What could possibly be her motivation?
我一点也不无趣
I'm not boring!
你真是只强悍的母兽
You magnificent she-beast.
我们的汗水和辛劳都得到回报了
All our sweaty passion and grunting paid off.
现在我该告诉你了  保拉是同性恋
Now's the time I should tell you. Paula is gay.
她交了个朋友
Aw. She made a friend.
你让我成为了一个全新的女人
You've made me a new woman.
我该担心吗
Oh. Should I be concerned?
不会比那次我们的膝盖
It's no weirder than that time
在吧台下面靠在一起更诡异
our knees touched under the bar.
你还记着这事吗
You still think about that?
每天都记着
Every day.
我很久都没这么开心了
Aw. I haven't been this happy in a long time.
你表现得很棒  不过我有个问题
You were great, but I have a question.
你想更上一层楼吗
Do you want to take it to the next level?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你愿意和我一起冒险吗
Will you ride the blade with me?
帮我打败那些有着锯齿的骗子
You know, help me bow the jagged-toothed fiddle?
我没听懂
I don't understand.
拖拽着危险致命的红杉树
Draw and drag the sequoia widowmaker.
widowmaker指折断却未坠落的大段树干  常致人员伤亡
你得明确告诉我你在说什么
You're gonna have to tell me what you're talking about.
你愿意在双头锯比赛中当我的搭档吗
Will you be my partner on the double-ended bucksaw?
你真的觉得我有这个本事吗
You really think that I have what it takes?
我知道你有
I know you do.
但是如果我们要参加
But if we do this,
你就得和我一起训练一个月  去波特兰
you'll have to train with me for a month, in Portland.
一个月  不行  我不能离开侯默那么久
A month? Oh, no, I can't leave Homer that long.
给孤儿们的铅笔
幻想可以这么美好吗
Oh. Fantasies can be good?
你终于回来了
Good to have you back.
天哪  累死了
Boy, am I beat.
侯默  我感觉
Homie, I feel like
我在比赛中成为了最好的自己
I'm my very best self in these competitions.
没错  亲爱的
You are, honey.
用一种我无法让你感受或理解的方式
In a way I could never make you feel or comprehend.
保拉想让我和她一起训练
Paula wants me to train with her.
如果我去的话  我要走一个月
If I do, I'll be gone for a month.
一个月  我们从来没有分开这么久
A month? We've never been apart that long.
我们不在同一扇旋转门里时我就会想你
I miss you when we're separated in a revolving door.
我穿衣服时  毛衣套住脑袋时我就会想你
I miss you when I'm putting a sweater over my head.
我打喷嚏时闭上眼睛的一瞬间会想你
I miss you when I close my eyes during a sneeze.
如果钟早了一小时响起我也会想你
I miss you when the clock springs ahead an hour.
因为我们无法一起度过那一小时了
We'll never get that time back.
侯默  你是真的希望我留下
Homer, do you really want me to stay,
明知道我有多需要它
knowing how much I need this
来获得自我满足感
to feel good about myself?
是的
Yes, I do.
怎么  我说错什么了
What? What?
你去哪  她是否就此一别永不相见
Where you going? She might leave and never come back.
像麦当劳烤汁猪排堡
Just like the McRib.
地址无效
由麦当劳转交给烤汁猪排堡
一个月后
波特兰机场  每天都有手工制作的飞机航班
波特兰
让波特兰保持怪异
伏都教甜甜圈
波特兰
如果伍迪·哈里森是座城市会怎样
别再搬来这
我忘记不锁门了
Oh. I forgot to unlock the door.
天啊  真是在侮辱别人
God, how insulting to people.
要见你们妈我好紧张
So nervous about seeing your mother.
享受波特兰吧
Let's just enjoy Portland.
难以置信我们都没来过
I mean, I can't believe we've never been here before.
本土工艺品  工艺酿酒厂
Indigenous artworks, craft breweries,
独立影院
independent movie theaters--
全包含在一家咖啡店里
and that's just in one coffee shop.
咖啡厅
含影院  松木啤酒  松诺茨自酿
这不是漫画男吗
Comic Book Guy?
我总来这充电
Yes, I often come here to recharge.
在波特兰我是古怪的  而不是讨厌的
In Portland I'm quirky, rather than objectionable.
你在这还卖漫画书吗
Do you sell comic books here?
不  我卖大麻和手工意大利腊肠
No. Marijuana. And artisanal salami.
含大麻的
Laced with marijuana.
昆毕街
科尔尼街
常青台742号
多尔夫街
勒弗乔伊街
范浩腾大道
弗兰德斯街
愚蠢的弗兰德斯街
Stupid Flanders Street.
到了  你们妈就住这
Okay, this is where your mom is.
帮我赢回她
Help me get her back.
求求了
Please help me get her back.
哇  尼古拉斯·凯奇
Ooh. Hello, Nicolas Cage.
爸爸  她知道那是假发
Dad, she's gonna know that's not your real hair.
你得对真实的自己有信心
You've got to have a modicum of faith in who you are.
"易如反掌"
It's a snap.
酷
Cool.
欢迎新朋友
Welcome, new friend,
无论你是谁
whoever you are.
老侯
Homie!
你们提前一天到了
You're here a day early.
妈妈
Mom!
我想死你们了
Mm. Oh, I've missed you all so much.
你们怎么样
How are you guys?
我们当然是崩溃啦
Oh! We were, of course, unraveling.
巴仔  丽莎  爷爷会好好照顾你俩的
Bart, Lisa, your grampa is taking good care of you.
阿麦去哪了
Now where's the baby?
乖孩子
Aw. Good girl.
我喜欢你的穿着
Um, I like what you're wearing.
谢谢  这都是本地粗布服
Thank you. These are locally-sourced dungarees
和彭德尔顿法兰绒
and Pendleton flannel.
吉尔·索布尔在水晶舞厅演奏时就穿这样
It's what Jill Sobule wore when she played the Crystal Ballroom.
美国创作型歌手
写过《我亲了一个女孩》
吉尔·索布尔吗
Jill Sobule?
就像我们去过的其他地方  我爱波特兰
Like every other place we go, I love Portland.
太爱了  我想离开春田镇
So much, I want to leave Springfield
直到有坏事发生令我意识到
until I find out something bad that makes me realize
还是家最好
that there's no place like home.
别瞎说  妈妈没定居在这
Now, now, your mother has not settled in here.
欢迎
Welcome.
这是我俩的哈巴狗  耐克和对号
These are our pugs: Nike and Swoosh.
她  她
针织帽  别的衣物
加奈儿·梦奈
《女子监狱》  《拉字至上》  《人人都爱TIG》
布林茅尔女校
克丽·杜瓦尔
《拉字至上》演员
我们能行
马姬  能跟我来后院一下吗
Marjorie, could you and I have a word in the backyard?
你还意识不到这里的状况吗
Don't you see what's happening here?
-你结婚了  -我知道啊
- You're married. - Yes, I know.
是啊  嫁给你了
To you.
不是  是嫁给她了  看看四周
No, to her. Look around.
有两个重点表明  你已经嫁给了她
You're married in the two most important ways there are:
情绪不稳定和做饭
emotionally and cooking.
太荒谬了
Oh. That's ridiculous.
你们还养哈巴狗
You're fostering pugs.
它们让我想起你
They remind me of you.
但我很沮丧  我终于找到擅长的事
But I am upset. I'm finally good at something
但你却要感到嫉妒
and you have to be jealous.
马姬  甜心  我很为你骄傲
Marge, sweetie, I'm really proud of you.
我既不嫉妒也不生气
I'm not jealous or mad.
只是...你什么时候回家
It's just... when are you coming home?
明天  比赛之后
Tomorrow, after the competition.
我赢啦
Woo-hoo! I win.
我可没担心过
Not that I was nervous.
协助自杀诊所
除非我们赢了  那样的话
Unless we win, in which case,
我可能要留在那准备决赛
I might stay and prep for the finals.
马姬  我从第一天开始就在支持你
Marge, I've backed you in this from day one.
不  你没有  一点也没有
No, you haven't. Not a bit.
那现在开始也有点晚了
Then it's too late to start now.
联邦康普茶储备
麦片与坚果博物馆
我坐在酒吧里
Oh, I'm sitting in a bar
而我的妻子却爱上了一个女伐木工
and my wife's in love with a female lumberjack.
很有波特兰的风格  你是哪里人
Classic Portland. Where are you from?
春田镇
Springfield.
-哪一个  俄勒冈的吗  -我不知道
- Which one? Oregon? - I don't know.
欢迎来到格雷兹利伐木运动
Welcome back to the Grizzly Timbersports
西北赛区总决赛的现场
Northwest Championship Finals,
本次比赛不由任何人倾情赞助
brought to you by no one.
我们还在找赞助商
Still looking.
马姬和保拉状态很稳
Marge and Paula are in control.
我爱上了这项运动
I am falling in love with this sport.
而我如果爱  就深爱
And when I fall, I fall hard.
我要把你带回家
I'm taking you home with me.
等等  等等  朋友们
Hold the Stella, fella.
卡罗尔·橡·康纳和瑞秋·松·科恩
Carol "Oak" Connor and Rachel "The Pine" Cohen
成为了第一
have taken command.
我不能沉默下去了  让我过去
I can't be silent anymore. Let me through.
地方不是挺大的吗
Eh. There's plenty of room.
马姬  我是个废木工
Marge, I was a lumber-jerk.
只有你快乐我才会快乐
I'm only happy if you're happy.
我们之间的爱就像一棵老树
Our love is like an old tree.
如果你砍倒它  它只会重生得更顽强
If you cut it down, it grows back stronger.
树可不是那么长的
Um, that's not how trees work.
但根据我的书  它就是
Well, according to my book, it is.
《树是怎么长的》
真棒
Yay! All right.
我爱这项运动
I love this sport!
也许现在我可以爱我的伐木工儿子了
And maybe now I can love my lumberjack son.
女士们先生们  我们的冠军
Ladies and gentlemen, our grand champion
以及福步户外商店50美元礼品卡的获得者是
and winner of a Bass Pro Shops $50 gift card,
马姬·辛普森
Marge Simpson.
可以啊  冠军
All right, champ!
浴室见
See you in the showers.
恭喜你  保拉  你赢了
Congratulations, Paula. You won.
享受到死吧你...
Enjoy the hell out of it...
侯默  你为什么觉得我赢了
Homer, what is it that you think that I've won?
和我一起  马姬是个不错的女人
With me, Marge is a good woman.
和你一起  马姬是有两条很棒的狗的优秀女人
With you, Marge is a great woman with two awesome dogs.
我对马姬没兴趣
I'm not interested in Marge.
我有妻子和孩子的
I have a wife and a kid.
你有妻子
You have a wife?
她在东京  为备战奥林匹克训练
She's in Tokyo, training for the Olympics.
她拿着那种彩带跳舞
She dances... with the ribbons?
我不知道那叫什么
I don't know what it's called.
所以你不打算拆散我们
So you're not breaking us up?
不  我是说  我会想念她在木锯那头的样子的
No. I mean, I'll miss her on the other end of the bucksaw,
也会十分想念那80块的冠军奖金
and I'll really miss that $80 grand prize money,
但这里很欢迎她
but she's welcome to come up here
随时过来训练
and train any time.
我太感谢你了
I am so grateful.
我想为你做点什么
I want to do something for you.
如果你还想要个孩子的话
If you'd like another kid,
我很乐意提供我的精子
I am more than happy to offer up my sperm.
你的好意我心领了  但是...
That's very kind, but...
不  说真的  我一直想要一个
No really, I've always wanted to have a kid
可以不用负责的孩子
with no responsibilities.
好吧  你在前三名候选人里
All right. You're in the top three.
要么是你  要么是田径明星  要么是哈佛教授
It's you, the track star or the Harvard professor.
我懂了
Oh, I get it.
比起精子  精液会不会更好一点
Instead of sperm, would you like semen?
它们是一样的
They're the same thing.
是嘛  这样啊
They are? Uh-oh.
还是感觉很奇怪
Oh, it still feels weird.
我不知道该和她说什么
I don't know what to say to her.
我永远都想不到这句话
I never would've thought of that.
宝贝  你想回家吗
Honey, would you like to come home?
好吧
Aw. Okay.
爸爸爱你  小可爱
Your daddy loves you, sweetie.
他希望你永远都是一个强大自信的小公主
he wants to make sure you're always a strong, confident little lady.
所以我出去给你买了这个
So I went out and got you this!
玩具链锯
她的脑袋掉了
Aw, her baby head fell out.
美国民间传说  如果换牙时把乳牙放在枕头下面
就会得到牙仙子送的礼物
掌管脑袋的仙子会来拜访你的
You'll be getting a visit from the Head Fairy.